learnelementsnow.com 2016-11-02

# Learn Adobe Elements | Privacy

We Respect Your Privacy!

We will never sell, rent, or otherwise abuse your e-mail address or personal details. They will be used solely for the purpose of sending you the LearnElementsNow.com newsletter and occasional advertising letters. (We send these letters ourselves; we do not share your address or any information about you with the advertiser.) Should you wish to unsubscribe at any time, instructions on how to do so are included with every e-mail.

………………………………………………………………………..

Here’s our full privacy policy (for anyone with the inclination to read it)…

WEB SITE TERMS OF USE AND LEGAL NOTICES

Wow! You actually came to this page. Our lawyers made us include it and made us use a precious button on our home page to get you here. At first, we thought the lawyers were a real pain. But then we read the page. What a Netwakening! It’s really important stuff. We took the legalese the lawyers wrote and translated it into readable English. So be a smart nethead and read the stuff on this page. It could prevent you from hearing from our lawyers, or worse yet, from really nasty people, like prosecutors.

OUR PRIVACY POLICY

LearnElementsNow.com is committed to protecting the privacy of our online visitors. We collect information from online visitors who ask to be on our newsletter mailing list and/or receive periodic email announcements or free reports. Anyone who wishes can choose to be removed from our mailing list at any time. Each email will always contain a simple unsubscribe link.

All online visitor data collected by LearnElementsNow.com is protected against unauthorized access. We will not sell, trade, or give your personal information to other companies or organizations.

Children’s Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems. LearnElementsNow.com encourages parents to go online with their kids. Here are a few tips to help make a child’s online experience safer:

Teach kids never to give personal information, unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult. Includes name, address, phone, school, etc.

Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate.

Look for Web site privacy policies. Know how your child’s information is treated.

Check out the FTC’s site: http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/edcams/kidzprivacy/index.html for more tips on protecting children’s privacy online.

Contacting Us.  
We can be reached by contacting: LearnElementsNow.com,  Email: learnadobeelementsnow@gmail.com

1st January 2008

LearnElementsNow.com
